# Yode Wang

## **UX** Designer

yode0419@gmail.com.tw

+886 911 027827

https://yode0419.github.io/portfolio



## **Profile**

I am a entry-level designer, a challenger in the field of UX design, with a background in civil structural engineering. Despite the different fields, I possess core capabilities required in this area: communication and coordination, design thinking, and problem-solving. Drawing, 3D modeling, presenting ideas, and considering feasibility are my specialties.

During my journey of self-study for this career transition, I have completed the Google UX Design course, accumulated UX portfolio projects, and built up my personal website. I am excited to bring my passion to UX and product design, aiming to provide users with enhanced experiences.

## **Experiences**

2023.06 - 2023.08 Google UX Design Professional Certificate

Learning UX / Portfolio / Web Development

2016.09 - 2023.06 Structural Engineer

TYLIN Construction Consultant
Structural Design / Bridge Design/Project Management

- · Taoyuan Metro Green Line
- · Kaohsiung Metro Red Line
- · Taoyuan Airport Terminal 3
- · Hualien-Taitung Railway Dual-Track Project

2019.13 - 2020.12 Working Holiday in Australia

Perth / Melbourne

- · Crazy Sales Warehouse
- · The Pamphleteers Mail Delivery
- · Treviso Farm Grape Worker

### Education

2013.09 - 2015.09 National Taiwan University

Master's Degree in Civil Engineering, Structural Division

2009.09 - 2013.09 National Taiwan University

**AutoCAD** 

Bachelor's Degree in Civil Engineering

### Skills

Graphic Design	3D Modeling	Front-End	Office	Languages
Figma	Blender	Development	Word	English
Photoshop	SketchUp	HTML	PowerPoint	(Intermediate Level)
Illustrator		CSS	Excel	French
Procreate	Engineering	JavaScript	VBA	(Beginner Level)
	Drawing	Bootstrap		(20907 2000)